巨大的  跳动的阴茎
giant, throbbing penis,
还有什么比这更具文化冲击性
what could be more counterculture?
看起来就像根热狗  而且字体也很丑
It looks like a hot dog. And the lettering sucks.
任何革命的诞生都没有经过精心包装
Revolutions don't come wrapped in a cute ribbon.
你想打倒强权
You want to bring down power structures?
你想给那些兜售迂腐思想的人
You want to get in the face of people
来一次沉重的打击
who are peddling corroded ideals?
你需要一件制服  来大声表达你真实的心声
You need a uniform that screams authenticity.
我们没有花过一分钱
We didn't pay Chinese factory orphans
让中国的孤儿童工做这些东西
three cents an hour to make these.
而是在我们自己的客厅
No, this is our living room.
用自己的双手  自己的努力
Our hands. Our sweat.
这就是草根阶级
Talk about grassroots.